Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Collection of Male Photographers in the American West
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Materials, circa 1840-2003; Series II; (231 boxes)
  - Photographic Materials
    - Heering, John Hermann, 3 (Box 411)
    - Heller, Louis Herman, 11 (Box 412)
    - Hemenway & Stephenson (Box 411)
    - Hemenway, O. (Box 411)
    - Hemenway, Walter (Box 411)
    - Hemingway, J. W. (Box 411)
    - Hemminger's (Box 411)
    - Hemmings, C. B. (Box 411)
    - Hendee, Denny H. (Box 411)
    - Hendee, E. B. (Box 411)
    - Henfield, John (Box 411)
    - Henriod, Gustave Louis Edward (Box 411)
    - Henry & Burnett (Box 411)
    - Henry, James E. (Box 411)
    - Henry, W. A. (Box 411)
    - Henry, W. F. (Box 411)
    - Henry's Camera Corporation (Box 411)
    - Herbruger, Emil (Box 411)
    - Hess, Ed. (Box 411)
    - Heywood & Towers (Box 411)
    - Heywood, John D. (Box 411)
    - Heywood, S. J. (Box 411)
    - Hickox (Box 411)
    - Hicks & Company (Box 411)
    - Hicks & Starring (Box 411)
    - Hicks, John Ross (Box 411)
    - Higgins & Howland (Box 411)
    - Higgins & Johnston (Box 411)
    - Higgins, E. R. (Box 411)
    - Higgins, Thomas J. (Box 411)
    - Higinbotham, John Baptiste (Box 411)
    - Hildreth, James T. (Box 411)
    - Hiler, Milo (Box 411)
    - Hill & DeJoines (Box 413)
    - Hill & Franklin (Box 413)
    - Hill & Yard (Box 413)
    - Hill, Andrew Putnam (Box 413)
    - Hill, W. H. (Box 413)
    - Hills, Rufus (Box 413)
    - Hirsch & Kaiser (Box 413)
    - Hirsch & Kaye (Box 413)
    - Hirsch, Alphonso (Box 413)
    - Hitchcock, George G. (Box 413)
    - Hodapp and Zuber (Box 413)
    - Hodgkins, George Washington (Box 413)
    - Hodson (Box 413)
    - Hodson, Burton M., 9 (Box 414)
    - Hodson, Burton M. (Box 415)
    - Hodson, John R., 11 (Box 416)
    - Hoebel & Luther (Box 413)
    - Hoelke, Hermann E. (Box 413)
    - Hoffman, John Miller (Box 413)
    - Hoffman's Studio (Box 413)
    - Hogan, D. C. (Box 413)
    - Hogan, John H. (Box 413)
    - Hoien (Box 413)
    - Holler, Joseph, 6 (Box 417)
    - Hollymont Cut-Rate Drugs (Box 413)
    - Holly-Tints (Box 413)
    - Hollywood Nite Club Photos (Box 413)
    - Hollywood Studio (Box 413)
    - Holmes (Box 413)
    - Holmes Photo Company (Box 413)
    - Holmes, Alex (Box 413)
    - Holmes, R. R. R. (Box 413)
    - Holmes, Samuel (Box 413)
    - Holt, D. (Box 413)
    - Hoogs, Octavian (Box 413)
    - Hooper, Harry S. (Box 413)
    - Hopps, W. S. (Box 413)
    - Horn & Mears (Box 413)
    - Horn, John Patrick (Box 413)
    - Horne, R. W. (Box 413)
    - Hornzee (Box 413)
    - Hosmer, Harrie B. (Box 413)
    - Houghton (Box 413)
    - Houseworth, Thomas, 34 (Box 418)
    - Houseworth, Thomas (Box 419)
    - Houston & Howland (Box 420)
    - Houston, H. B. (Box 420)
    - Hovey Prints (Box 420)
    - Howard, Elton (Box 420)
    - Howard, J. S. (Box 420)
    - Howe, J. Milton (Box 420)
    - Howell, Edgar Wade (Box 420)
    - Howes (Box 420)
    - Howes, Samuel P. (Box 420)
    - Howland & Dewey Company (Box 421)
    - Howland & Fagersteen (Box 421)
    - Howland & Lonergan (Box 421)
    - Howland, Benjamin Franklin, 10 (Box 421)
    - Howland, Clarence A. (Box 421)
    - Howlett Studios (Box 422)
    - Hoyt & Hiram (Box 422)
    - Hubbell, & Company (Box 422)
    - Hucks, T. G. (Box 423)
    - Huddleston, Foster G. (Box 422)
    - Hughes, Jim (Box 422)
    - Hulse, George C. (Box 422)
    - Hunt, Horace E. (Box 422)
    - Hunt, Kenn (Box 422)
    - Hunt, Orris P. (Box 422)
    - Hunter, J. W. (Box 422)
    - Hupp & Loundagin (Box 422)
    - Hupp, P. (Box 422)
    - Hurd, E. (Box 422)
    - Hurley (Box 422)
    - Hustlers, The (Box 422)
    - Huston, J. M. (Box 422)
    - Hutchings & Crum (Box 422)
    - Hutchings Photo Car (Box 422)
    - Hutton, James Dempsey (Box 422)
    - Hyland (Box 422)
    - Hyperion Gallery (Box 422)
    - Ideal Portrait Studio (Box 424)
    - Ideal Studio (Box 424)
    - Illingworth, William Henry (Box 424)
    - Imai, T. (Box 424)
    - Imperial Gallery, The, 15 (Box 425)
    - Ingersoll, William B. (Box 424)
    - International Gallery (Box 424)
    - Irish (Box 424)
    - Ironmonger, Charles F. (Box 424)
    - Irvin, George Cole (Box 424)
    - Ishiguro (Box 424)
    - Issati (Box 424)
    - Ives & Hunt (Box 424)
    - Ives, E. H. (Box 424)
    - Jackson, C. N. (Box 426)
    - Jackson, J. J. (Box 426)
    - Jackson, William Henry (Box 426)
    - Jacobs' Studio (Box 426)
    - Jacobs, James Monroe, 7 (Box 427)
    - Jacoby, H. J. (Box 426)
    - Jacoby, J. F. (Box 426)
    - James Photo Service (Box 426)
    - James, George Wharton, 4 (Box 428)
    - James, James B. (Box 426)
    - James, William E. (Box 426)
    - Jarvis, B. & Son, 4 (Box 429)
    - Jefferson, Charles G. (Box 426)
    - Jenkins, John Carson (Box 426)
    - Johns, William F. (Box 430)
    - Johnson & Company (Box 430)
    - Johnson & Sullivan (Box 430)
    - Johnson Brothers (Box 430)
    - Johnson Photo Company (Box 430)
    - Johnson Studio, 3 (Box 431)
    - Johnson, A. J., 5 (Box 432)
    - Johnson, Amasa Parker (Box 430)
    - Johnson, Bryan R. (Box 430)
    - Johnson, C. O. (Box 430)
    - Johnson, Charles Wallace Jacob, 19 (Box 433)
    - Johnson, Charles Wallace Jacob (Box 434)
    - Johnson, Edward D. (Box 430)
    - Johnson, George H., 2 (Box 435)
    - Johnson, J. E. (Box 430)
    - Johnson, James B., 4 (Box 436)
    - Johnson, Josiah (Box 430)
    - Johnson, W. P. (Box 430)
    - Johnston & Company (Box 437)
    - Johnston & Crigler (Box 437)
    - Johnston & Howes (Box 437)
    - Johnston & Simas (Box 437)
    - Johnston & Strunz (Box 437)
    - Johnston, James W. (Box 437)
    - Johnston, Richard T. (Box 437)
    - Johnston, W. & Company (Box 437)
    - Jones & Kennet (Box 437)
    - Jones & Lotz, 7 (Box 438)
    - Jones' Photoscope of CA (Box 437)
    - Jones, Paul B. (Box 437)
    - Jones, Robinson & Company, 2 (Box 437)
    - Jones, Rodney C. (Box 437)
    - Jones, Rulofson & Company (Box 437)
    - Jones, Thomas Hugh (Box 437)
    - Jordan (Box 437)
    - Joslin, Amen J. T. (Box 437)
    - Jossa, C. A. (Box 437)
    - Josselyn, Lewis (Box 437)
    - Joy Family, 3 (Box 439)
    - Judd, Chauncy (Box 437)
    - Judkins, David Roby, 6 (Box 437)
    - Junk & Leslie (Box 437)
    - Justus (Box 437)
    - Kahn, George H. (Box 440)
    - Kahn, Henry (Box 440)
    - Kalb (Box 440)
    - Kamera-Art Service (Box 440)
    - Kamiyama, Frank (Box 440)
    - Kanzee, George (Box 440)
    - Karras, Max, 4 (Box 441)
    - Kashower, M. & Company (Box 440)
    - Kay, Wallace, 2 (Box 440)
    - Keefer, Henry (Box 440)
    - Keller, Herman, 2 (Box 440)
    - Kellogg, Gilles P. (Box 440)
    - Kelly & Sobieski (Box 440)
    - Kelsey, C. O. (Box 440)
    - Kemp (Box 440)
    - Kemp & Clarke (Box 440)
    - Kemp & Coleman (Box 440)
    - Kemp & Kluit (Box 440)
    - Kemp van E., H., 2 (Box 440)
    - Kemp, Edward H. (Box 440)
    - Kemp, H. (Box 440)
    - Kemp, John Charles, 2 (Box 440)
    - Kendall (Box 440)
    - Kendall & Clinch (Box 440)
    - Kendall, R. A., 2 (Box 440)
    - Kennell-Ellis (Box 440)
    - Kerlin, Theodore J. (Box 440)
    - Kerr, Daniel (Box 440)
    - Kervel (Box 440)
    - Keystone View Company, 5 (Box 442)
    - Kiefer & Sammis (Box 443)
    - Kilburn, B. W. (Box 443)
    - Kildare, Edward J. (Box 443)
    - King Brothers (Box 443)
    - King, Joseph W. (Box 443)
    - Kingsley, John Lucas (Box 443)
    - Kinman, J. F. (Box 443)
    - Kipps, Alfred Kemble (Box 443)
    - Kirk, Geary & Company (Box 443)
    - Kirk, H. P. (Box 443)
    - Kirkpatrick, Fred (Box 443)
    - Kiser, Fred H. (Box 443)
    - Klain, Nathaniel Michael, 2 (Box 443)
    - Klindt, Charles (Box 443)
    - Klug, Eugene F. (Box 443)
    - Knight & Johnson (Box 443)
    - Knight, George H. (Box 443)
    - Knowles, D. N. (Box 443)
    - Knowlton, George (Box 443)
    - Koeber, Paul C. Company (Box 443)
    - Kohler, C. A. (Box 443)
    - Kohler, C. F. (Box 443)
    - Kohler, Eugene (Box 443)
    - Kolb Brothers Studio (Box 443)
    - Konrad, L. (Box 443)
    - Kracaw, Austin (Box 443)
    - Kraft, E. (Box 443)
    - Kraus, Henry D. (Box 443)
    - Kusel, Edward Abraham, 2 (Box 443)
    - Kuster, H. (Box 443)
    - Kuykendall, Frank, 2 (Box 443)
    - La Roche, F. (Box 444)
    - La Rosh & Tieman (Box 444)
    - La Salle (Box 444)
    - Lafayette Studio (Box 444)
    - Lainer, Charles, 9 (Box 445)
    - Lambert's Studio (Box 444)
    - Lamkin, Clyde C. (Box 444)
    - Lamson, J. H. (Box 444)
    - Lancy, Thomas C. (Box 444)
    - Landau, Robert (Box 444)
    - Lange, Oscar V., 2 (Box 444)
    - Langevin, Edward (Box 444)
    - Langhart, S. E. (Box 444)
    - Lare, C. (Box 444)
    - Larson (Box 444)
    - Lathrop, Frank H. (Box 444)
    - Latour, William (Box 444)
    - Lauck & Barnes (Box 444)
    - Lawrence & Houseworth, 22 (Box 446)
    - Lawrence & Son (Box 444)
    - Lawrence, C. S. (Box 444)
    - Lawrence, George E. (Box 444)
    - Lawrence, James A. (Box 444)
    - Lawson & Powers (Box 444)
    - Lawson, Toswell (Box 444)
    - Lawton, H. S. (Box 444)
    - Layne (Box 444)
    - Le Plongeon (Box 444)
    - Lea, D. P. (Box 444)
    - Leavenworth, John (Box 444)
    - Lee, Willard Malcolm (Box 444)
    - Lees, Isaiah W. (Box 444)
    - Leet, R. A. & Company (Box 444)
    - Leftwich, John W., 3 (Box 444)
    - Leisenring, James B. (Box 444)
    - Lentz, William H. (Box 444)
    - Lenz, J. M. (Box 444)
    - Levy, I. G. (Box 444)
    - Lewis (Box 444)
    - Lewis, E. B., 2 (Box 447)
    - Ley, Thomas A., 2 (Box 448)
    - Liberty Studio (Box 449)
    - Lichtig & Agner (Box 449)
    - Liebert, Alphonse J. (Box 449)
    - Liljegreen, A. (Box 449)
    - Lindner (Box 449)
    - Lloyd, William S. (Box 449)
    - Locke, I. S. (Box 449)
    - Lockwood, R. (Box 449)
    - Lofland, David R. (Box 449)
    - Logan, C. W., 3 (Box 450)
    - Lohn, Albert W. (Box 449)
    - Lomen Bros. (Box 449)
    - London Stereoscopic Company (Box 449)
    - Long & Scott (Box 449)
    - Long, E. (Box 449)
    - Longpre, Paul de (Box 449)
    - Loomis, Arthur W. (Box 451)
    - Loomis, Benjamin F., 2 (Box 451)
    - Lorenz, J. A. (Box 451)
    - Loryea Brothers, 4 (Box 452)
    - Los Angeles News Company (Box 451)
    - Los Angeles Portrait Company (Box 451)
    - Los Angeles Scenic & View Company (Box 451)
    - Los Angeles Stereoscopic View Company (Box 451)
    - Loundagin (Box 451)
    - Lovejoy, William E., 2 (Box 451)
    - Lovewell (Box 451)
    - Lovewell, George H. (Box 451)
    - Lovewell, Samuel (Box 451)
    - Lovewell's Photographic (Box 451)
    - Lowry Brothers (Box 451)
    - Lucerne Studio (Box 451)
    - Ludlow, Frank G. (Box 451)
    - Lukins, W. W. (Box 451)
    - Lummis, C. F. (Box 451)
    - Luther, H. (Box 451)
    - Lynn, E. A. (Box 451)
    - M & M Studio (Box 453)
    - M & W Photo (Box 453)
    - Macaulay, John W. (Box 453)
    - Madison, G. F. (Box 453)
    - Main, O. F. (Box 453)
    - Mains & Johnson (Box 453)
    - Mains and Sampson (Box 453)
    - Mains and Shippy (Box 453)
    - Manning, T. A. (Box 453)
    - Marceau & Power (Box 453)
    - Marceau, Theodore C., 11 (Box 454)
    - Marden, Robert A. (Box 453)
    - Marie, Louis (Box 453)
    - Markoe, Roman (Box 453)
    - Marks, Robert W., 5 (Box 455)
    - Marshall, William (Box 453)
    - Marston, Charles Albert (Box 453)
    - Martel-Howlett (Box 453)
    - Martin (Box 453)
    - Martin & Fox (Box 453)
    - Martin & Thullen (Box 453)
    - Martin, Edward (Box 453)
    - Martin, Frederick W. (Box 453)
    - Martin, V. Covert, 6 (Box 456)
    - Masters & Company (Box 453)
    - Masters, William G. (Box 453)
    - Mathews, H. E. (Box 453)
    - Mathiason, P. B. (Box 453)
    - Matthews, C. L. (Box 453)
    - Maude, Frederic Hamer (Box 453)
    - Maurer, Oscar (Box 453)
    - Maxwell (Box 453)
    - Maxwell & Dorr (Box 453)
    - Maxwell and Mudge, 7 (Box 457)
    - Maxwell Bros. (Box 453)
    - Maxwell Darrow and Company (Box 453)
    - Maxwell, P. (Box 453)
    - Maxwell, William Audley (Box 453)
    - May and Fesenden's (Box 453)
    - May and Nye (Box 453)
    - May, George Washington (Box 453)
    - May, Hamilton J. (Box 453)
    - Mayo, Oscar (Box 453)
    - May's Photo Studio (Box 453)
    - McAllister & Brother (Box 458)
    - McCafferty (Box 458)
    - McCarthy, Charles E. (Box 458)
    - McClaire, M. S. (Box 458)
    - McClearie, William (Box 458)
    - McClellan, William C. (Box 458)
    - McClelland (Box 458)
    - McCormick, John C. (Box 458)
    - McCrary, Sylvester Hall (Box 458)
    - McCullagh, E. J., 3 (Box 458)
    - McCurry Foto Company (Box 458)
    - McCutchan, M. J. (Box 458)
    - McDonald, A. J., 3 (Box 458)
    - McEvoy, John James (Box 458)
    - McFarlin and Monwell (Box 458)
    - McFarlin, S. L., 2 (Box 458)
    - McGee, Jas H. (Box 458)
    - McGinley, T. B., 2 (Box 458)
    - McGinnis, Jack (Box 458)
    - McIntyre, Sterling C. (Box 458)
    - McKay (Box 458)
    - McKean and Ort, 3 (Box 458)
    - McKinnon, M. A. (Box 458)
    - McKown, George W. (Box 458)
    - McLaughlin, J. G. (Box 458)
    - McLellan, Robert (Box 458)
    - McMahon, B. (Box 458)
    - McMillan, 2 (Box 459)
    - McMillan Bros. (Box 459)
    - McMillan, Charles, 2 (Box 459)
    - McMillan, F. H., 2 (Box 459)
    - McMillan, J. W. (Box 459)
    - McMillan, John (Box 459)
    - Meddaugh, O. E. (Box 460)
    - Medina, F. (Box 460)
    - Mehlin (Box 460)
    - Melliar (Box 460)
    - Memphis Gallery (Box 460)
    - Mendelssohn (Box 460)
    - Mendenhall, Herbert (Box 460)
    - Mendoza, Julius D. (Box 460)
    - Mercury Photo (Box 460)
    - Merriam, Ezra Daly (Box 460)
    - Merserau, Fred (Box 460)
    - Mesarvey (Box 460)
    - Metcalf & Hutchinson (Box 460)
    - Meyer, Charles A. (Box 460)
    - Meyer, E. L. (Box 460)
    - Middlemiss, B. (Box 460)
    - Mikesell, Gus (Box 460)
    - Miles-Hollister (Box 460)
    - Miller & Chase (Box 460)
    - Miller, C. R. (Box 460)
    - Miller, Milton M. (Box 460)
    - Miller, William P. (Box 460)
    - Miltz and Overton (Box 460)
    - Miltz and Swart (Box 460)
    - Miltz, Swart, & Schad (Box 460)
    - Miltz, Wenzin, & Company (Box 460)
    - Miner, George H. & Company (Box 460)
    - Mitchell, 3 (Box 460)
    - Mitchell, Edward H., 2 (Box 460)
    - Mitchell, L. J. (Box 460)
    - Mitchell, Walter Jr. (Box 460)
    - Mojoiner, A. L. (Box 460)
    - Moller, J. B. (Box 460)
    - Monaco, John B., 5 (Box 461)
    - Monaco, Louis P., 3 (Box 461)
    - Monaco, Marino, 9 (Box 461)
    - Monahan, William (Box 462)
    - Monfort, Aschylus William (Box 462)
    - Monmonier, W. B., 2 (Box 462)
    - Monroe and Potter (Box 462)
    - Monsen, Frederick I. (Box 462)
    - Monteverde, F. E. (Box 462)
    - Mooers & Galt (Box 462)
    - Mooers, William A. (Box 462)
    - Moore, Arthur R. (Box 462)
    - Moore, E. W. (Box 462)
    - Moore, Edgar B., 4 (Box 463)
    - Moore, G. E. (Box 462)
    - Morgan, Fred S. (Box 462)
    - Morrill, Edwin (Box 462)
    - Morris, B. Y. (Box 462)
    - Morse, George Daniels, 24 (Box 464)
    - Morse, George Daniels (Box 465)
    - Mortensen, William (Box 462)
    - Morton, L. (Box 462)
    - Motoyoshi, H. T. (Box 462)
    - Moulin, Gabriel (Box 462)
    - Moyemont & Biebes (Box 462)
    - Mudge, Archie C. (Box 462)
    - Mueller (Box 462)
    - Mullen, Chester Jerome (Box 462)
    - Mullender & Young (Box 462)
    - Munsey, Fred E. (Box 462)
    - Murillo (Box 462)
    - Mushet, Edward R. (Box 462)
    - Mutual Label and Lithographic Company (Box 462)
    - Muybridge, Eadweard James, 13 (Box 466)
    - Myers, C. A. (Box 462)
    - N & L Company (Box 467)
    - Nahl Bros., 2 (Box 467)
    - Nast, J. E. (Box 467)
    - Nelson (Box 467)
    - Nelson Studio (Box 467)
    - Nelson, C. A. (Box 467)
    - Nelson, G. R. (Box 467)
    - Nelson, Ivan (Box 467)
    - Nesemann, E. (Box 467)
    - New Studio (Box 469)
    - New York Gallery, 6 (Box 468)
    - Newcomb (Box 469)
    - Newdick, A. P. (Box 469)
    - Newman Post Card Company (Box 469)
    - Newman Studio (Box 469)
    - Newton, E. B. (Box 469)
    - Neymann, Percy (Box 469)
    - Nichols Photo (Box 469)
    - Nichols, Sheldon K. (Box 469)
    - Nicolet, Fred (Box 469)
    - Nicoulin, J. F. (Box 469)
    - Ninnis, Fred C. (Box 469)
    - Noble, S. S. (Box 469)
    - Noe, Charles B. (Box 469)
    - Noe, J. S., 3 (Box 469)
    - Noe, Miguel, Jr. (Box 469)
    - Noel, Adelard (Box 469)
    - Norcross, Oliver H. P. (Box 469)
    - Norcross, W. F. (Box 469)
    - North Beach Photo Company (Box 469)
    - Northern California Council of Camera Clubs (Box 469)
    - Novelty Photo Company, 3 (Box 469)
    - Nowack, M. (Box 469)
    - Noyes, David P. (Box 469)
    - Nusbaum, A. B. C. (Box 469)
    - Nye & Bisbee (Box 469)
    - Oak Park Tin Type Gallery (Box 470)
    - Oakland Camera Club (Box 470)
    - Oakland Photo Engravers' Union (Box 470)
    - Ocean Beach Gallery (Box 470)
    - O'Connor, Joseph R. (Box 470)
    - Offield, H. G. (Box 470)
    - Ogelvie, B. (Box 470)
    - Old Mission Studio (Box 470)
    - Olmsted, Philander A. (Box 470)
    - Olsen, H. J. (Box 470)
    - Oltman, John (Box 470)
    - Omega Foto Company (Box 470)
    - Opposition Gallery (Box 470)
    - Orange Studio (Box 470)
    - Oregon State Highway Commission (Box 470)
    - Oriental Photographic Parlors (Box 470)
    - Oriental Studio (Box 470)
    - Ormsby, E. D., 5 (Box 471)
    - Osborn, Walter (Box 470)
    - Osborne & Company (Box 470)
    - Osborne, A. W. (Box 470)
    - Osburn & Searles (Box 470)
    - Ottnat, Jacob D. (Box 470)
    - Otto, Ernst A. (Box 470)
    - Owens, T. (Box 470)
    - Owl Drug Company (Box 470)
    - Oxford Studio (Box 470)
    - Pacific Coast Photography and View Company (Box 472)
    - Pacific Gallery (Box 472)
    - Pacific Novelty Company (Box 472)
    - Pacific Ocean Beach Company (Box 472)
    - Pacific Photo & Button Company (Box 472)
    - Pacific Photograph Car (Box 472)
    - Pacific Pictoral News Service (Box 472)
    - Pacific Studio (Box 472)
    - Pacific View Company (Box 472)
    - Paffrath Portraits (Box 472)
    - Page, William D. (Box 472)
    - Painter (Box 472)
    - Palace Art Gallery (Box 472)
    - Palace of Art (Box 472)
    - Palace Photo Studio (Box 472)
    - Palm Studio, 2 (Box 472)
    - Palmer, A. Ray (Box 472)
    - Palmer, J. D. (Box 472)
    - Palmer's Studio (Box 472)
    - Paralta Photo Service (Box 472)
    - Paralta Studio (Box 472)
    - Park, F. L. (Box 472)
    - Parker (Box 472)
    - Parker & Hasselman (Box 472)
    - Parker & Knight (Box 472)
    - Parker and Parker (Box 472)
    - Parker, F. (Box 472)
    - Parker, Harold A. (Box 472)
    - Parkhurst, T. Harmon (Box 473)
    - Parks Photo Studio (Box 473)
    - Parrish, Bird (Box 473)
    - Parsons, D. H. (Box 473)
    - Partridge, Samuel C. (Box 473)
    - Passavant Printing Company (Box 473)
    - Patterson, Frank (Box 473)
    - Paxton, Andrew B. (Box 473)
    - Payne (Box 473)
    - Payne & Monmonier (Box 473)
    - Payne & Parrott (Box 473)
    - Payne and Bagely (Box 473)
    - Payne, H. T. (Box 473)
    - Payne, Les (Box 473)
    - Payne, Stanton & Company (Box 473)
    - Peabody, H. G. (Box 473)
    - Peavey, Louis (Box 473)
    - Peek & Lagomarsino (Box 473)
    - Peerless Gallery (Box 473)
    - Peiser, Theodore E. (Box 473)
    - Pender & Company (Box 473)
    - Penelon, Henri Joseph (Box 473)
    - Peninsula Photo Supply (Box 473)
    - Perkins & Foss (Box 473)
    - Perkins, A. J., 2 (Box 474)
    - Perry (Box 473)
    - Perry & Kelly (Box 473)
    - Perry, Ira C. (Box 475)
    - Perspecto (Box 473)
    - Petaluma Photo Parlors (Box 473)
    - Peters, John Henry, 10 (Box 476)
    - Peterson, C. E. (Box 477)
    - Phares, M. E. (Box 477)
    - Phares, William H. (Box 477)
    - Philadelphia Gallery (Box 477)
    - Philippi, R. J. (Box 477)
    - Phillips, John H. (Box 477)
    - Phoenix Art Company (Box 477)
    - Phoenix Photo Engraving Company (Box 477)
    - Photo Mount & Card Manufacturing Company (Box 477)
    - Photo Movie Studio (Box 477)
    - Photo Post Card Company (Box 477)
    - Photo Sub-Post Card Company (Box 477)
    - Photocentral (Box 477)
    - Photographic Card Company (Box 477)
    - Photographic Parlors (Box 477)
    - Photomaton Studio (Box 477)
    - Photoreflex Studio (Box 477)
    - Piatt, C. E. (Box 477)
    - Pickett & Butler (Box 477)
    - Pickett, J. M. (Box 477)
    - Pierce & Blanchard (Box 477)
    - Pierce & Company (Box 477)
    - Pierce & McConnell (Box 477)
    - Pierce & Tilley (Box 477)
    - Pierce, C. C., 2 (Box 477)
    - Pierce, E. W. (Box 477)
    - Piggot & Shaw (Box 477)
    - Piggot, James Kenneth (Box 477)
    - Piggott & Sheppard (Box 477)
    - Pilliner & Hunter (Box 478)
    - Pilliner, W. H. (Box 478)
    - Pillsbury, A. C. (Box 478)
    - Piltz, Stanley, & Company (Box 478)
    - Pimentel, J. M. (Box 478)
    - Pinkham, Charles (Box 478)
    - Pinnell, Travis (Box 478)
    - Pioneer Gallery, 4 (Box 479)
    - Pitcher, J. (Box 478)
    - Pitts (Box 478)
    - Platt (Box 478)
    - Plaza Gallery (Box 478)
    - Pleasants, Joseph (Box 478)
    - Plecker, D. A. (Box 478)
    - Ploetz, J. (Box 478)
    - Plumbe, John (Box 478)
    - Pollock, J. T. (Box 478)
    - Pomeroy, Edgar (Box 478)
    - Pond, C. L. (Box 478)
    - Popular Photograph Parlor (Box 478)
    - Porter, David Arthur (Box 478)
    - Post (Box 478)
    - Postal Photo Company (Box 478)
    - Powell & Brown (Box 478)
    - Powell, L. M. (Box 480)
    - Precision Color Lab (Box 478)
    - Premium Postal Studio (Box 478)
    - Preston (Box 478)
    - Pretz, Jacob (Box 478)
    - Prezeau & Tougas (Box 478)
    - Price (Box 478)
    - Price & Ley (Box 478)
    - Price & Voelker (Box 478)
    - Price, Andrew, 5 (Box 481)
    - Prier, R. (Box 478)
    - Priest, C. F. (Box 478)
    - Prindle, Benjamin Augustus (Box 478)
    - Printing Corporation (Box 478)
    - Pro-Camera (Box 478)
    - Proctor, A. S. (Box 478)
    - Purnelle, H. J. (Box 478)
    - Purrington & Russell (Box 478)
    - Putnam Studio (Box 478)
    - Putnam, Arion (Box 478)
    - Putnam, Frank O. (Box 478)
    - Quigley, W. S. (Box 482)
    - Quirk & Bawden (Box 482)
    - Quirk & Halsey (Box 482)
    - Quirk, James (Box 482)
    - Rabe (Box 483)
    - Raisin City Studio (Box 483)
    - Ramos (Box 483)
    - Ramsey, Allen W. (Box 483)
    - Rands Bros. (Box 483)
    - Raney, A. L. (Box 483)
    - Rankin, George W. (Box 483)
    - Ransome, Fred (Box 483)
    - Rasmussen (Box 483)
    - Rea & Piggott (Box 483)
    - Rea, Thomas L. (Box 483)
    - Rea, William J. (Box 483)
    - Reall's Art Studio (Box 483)
    - Reddick, Ben (Box 483)
    - Redington, D. C. (Box 483)
    - Reed & Connell (Box 483)
    - Reed, Fred (Box 483)
    - Reed, J. Q. (Box 483)
    - Reed, Norman H., 2 (Box 484)
    - Reed, V. (Box 483)
    - Reed, W., 2 (Box 483)
    - Rees, Martin A. (Box 483)
    - Reese, ___ (Box 483)
    - Regel, William (Box 483)
    - Reid (Box 483)
    - Reiff, J. B. (Box 483)
    - Reilly, John James, 5 (Box 483)
    - Reinhart & Dorroth (Box 483)
    - Reinhart, John D. (Box 483)
    - Rembrandt Studio, 2 (Box 486)
    - Rendall, Stephan Arnold (Box 486)
    - Reyes (Box 486)
    - Reynolds (Box 486)
    - Reynolds, Kay Dee (Box 486)
    - Rhea (Box 486)
    - Rice, A. O. (Box 486)
    - Richards & Henry (Box 486)
    - Richards, J. D. (Box 486)
    - Richardson (Box 486)
    - Richardson & Atkins (Box 486)
    - Richardson, L. (Box 486)
    - Richert, W. C. (Box 486)
    - Richter, H. (Box 486)
    - Rick (Box 486)
    - Rieder, M., 2 (Box 486)
    - Rieman & Company, 4 (Box 487)
    - Rieman and Pray (Box 487)
    - Rieman and Tuttle (Box 487)
    - Rifenburg & Dowe (Box 488)
    - Rifenburg & Murphy (Box 488)
    - Rifenburg, A. G. (Box 488)
    - Riggs, J. W., 2 (Box 488)
    - Rile & Mensch (Box 488)
    - Rile, Henry France (Box 488)
    - Riley and Sherraden (Box 488)